<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolios on Phillip Stoneman</title><link>/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolios on Phillip Stoneman</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BHBN Sport</title><link>/portfolio/bhbn-sport/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/bhbn-sport/</guid><description>ABOUT THE WORK Since I started living in Birmingham, I wanted to continue my passion of "doing radio". I was recommended its hospital radio station, and joined the sport team as someone who knew the ins and outs of a studio, as opposed to a fan of football. However, I quickly developed my sporting punditry skills and would regularly host the four hour Saturday programme, driving the desk as if it was any other show that I had produced.</description></item><item><title>Demo</title><link>/portfolio/demo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/demo/</guid><description>ABOUT THE WORK I've worked around the radio industry for over five years, and have accrued substantial experience on-air – from presenting and producing my own show, to reading news and travel bulletins, and reporting from various locations, from charity events to a big (and almost world-record-setting) pair of pants. I am also more than happy to play second fiddle to a presenter, as a pundit or an additional voice to complement a piece.</description></item><item><title>Graphic Design</title><link>/portfolio/graphic-design/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/graphic-design/</guid><description>ABOUT THE WORK I have been using Adobe Photoshop regularly for nearly five years. From first playing around to create graphics for my student radio show, I regularly use it to assemble assets for BHBN Hospital Radio and was entrusted by Community Station Bay FM to turn their ideas in to visual form for use in promotional material. One of my favourite graphics designed almost from scratch was for a Capel’s Fish and Chips advert on a website banner for Bay FM.</description></item><item><title>Living Up The Weekend</title><link>/portfolio/living-up-the-weekend/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/living-up-the-weekend/</guid><description>ABOUT THE WORK My student radio show was arguably where it all began, in November 2012. From my first show, in my first year at RaW 1251AM, my weekly hobby soon blossomed in to one of the station's award-winning primetime shows, packed with plenty of production and quality content. I was able to hone my presenting style, focus my presenting strengths, and learn how best I could use the desk and playout system at my disposal to create a show full of energy and creativity, befitting our student audience over a Saturday lunchtime.</description></item><item><title>Station Sound</title><link>/portfolio/station-sound/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/portfolio/station-sound/</guid><description>ABOUT THE WORK I am BBC Hereford &amp; Worcester’s Station Sound producer; I've been making imaging for the radio station since late 2016. I have created the on-air sound of new programmes and many other programme refreshes, I introduced the new local radio jingle package to the station in 2021, and use on-air imaging to support key off-air campaigns across output. I combine long term planning and honing of campaigns with trails turned round to reflect the ‘vibe’ of the moment or promote the listen of future content across the station.</description></item></channel></rss>